A Guide to the Foundation for Child Development records FA019
Rockefeller Archive Center
Foundation for Child Development records
1898, 1902, 1907, 1909-1910, 1912-1998, bulk 1960-1998
bulk
Rockefeller Archive Center
Takanishi, Ruby
Zill, Nicholas
Wheatley, George M.
Cuyler, Lewis Baker
Clinton, Hillary Rodham
Emmet, Jessie K.
Dollard, Charles, 1907-1977
Birch, Herbert George, 1918-1973
Association for the Aid of Crippled Children
Foundation for Child Development
Blum, Barbara B.
Valdivieso, Rafael (Ray)
Swinyard, Chester A.
Senn, Milton J. E.
Sigal, Heidi
Moore, Evelyn
Richardson, Stephen A.
Lash, Trude W.
Kamerman, Sheila B.
Kagan, Jerome
Rockefeller, Mary French
Hetherington, E. Mavis (Eileen Mavis), 1926-
Hunter-Gault, Charlayne
Hecht, George J.
Brim, Orville Gilbert, 1883-1987
Bronfenbrenner, Urie, 1917-2005
FA019
42 Cubic Feet
Arrangement note
The Foundation for Child Development collection is arranged in six series:
Series 1 - Administration
Series 2 - Annual Reports
Series 3 - Financial Records
Series 4 - Grant Programs
Series 5 - Reprints
Series 6 - Audio-Visual Materials
Biographical/Historical note
The Foundation for Child Development had its origins in the Guild for the Crippled Children of the Poor of New York City (the Guild), an organization whose mission was to "care for the physical, social, domestic, educational, economic, and spiritual conditions of these unfortunates." It became the Association for the Aid of Crippled Children (AACC) in 1908, when it was established in New York City as a voluntary agency that sought to teach and aid disabled children who were victims of polio.
In the early twentieth century, physically disabled children were often homebound with no access to formal education. Mabel Irving Jones, a concerned citizen and advocate for these youngsters, provided the impetus behind the creation and eventual incorporation of an agency operating under the auspices of the New York City Children's Aid Society. By 1904 nearly 120 disabled school-aged children were attending school outside of the home; in 1906, Public School 104 of the New York City Board of Education operated the first public school class for crippled children. The Guild sought to treat those children neglected by hospitals and clinics and the "hundreds of chronic cases of crippled children whom these charities do not and cannot reach." The Guild cooperated with churches and other social services organizations including St. John's Guild, the Henrietta Industrial School, and the Hartley House Settlement, to teach children outside of the home, provide a luncheon meal, and return them to their homes. The Guild’s second Annual Report in 1898 indicated that this is the "first systematic effort ever made in New York City to give the crippled children out of institutions a helpful education."
Separated from the Children's Aid Society in 1908, the AACC was supported entirely by contributions and employed a staff of ten, led by trained nurses. In addition to providing transportation to school and health clinics and braces and other therapeutic devices, the AACC also established physical rehabilitation facilities. By 1940, over 30,000 children had benefited from these services, including children with cerebral palsy and other disorders of fetal and neonatal origin.
The organization’s early focus on the needs of a stranded school-aged population firmly defined its legacy. In later years, similar enterprises supported direct-care and research to benefit adult rehabilitation. The AACC joined with New York University-Bellevue Hospital to establish the Children's Division of the Institute of Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, today known as the Rusk Institute. During World War II, their pioneering work helped to rehabilitate injured soldiers.
In 1944, the AACC received an $11 million bequest from the Estate of Milo M. Belding, a silk manufacturer and banker whose donation honored his spouse, Annie K. Belding, a devoted volunteer and association board member for over twenty years. This bequest allowed the AACC to become a grant-making organization. Although the organization continued to provide direct services to children, in 1950 the Visiting Nurse Service of New York assumed this aspect of the agency’s services. Also during this period, the Association expanded its purview to include within its programs the developmentally disabled, the emotionally disturbed, and children with genetically based disorders, including circulatory and metabolic disorders. In 1962, it formed the Committee on Belding Scholars, with the specific goal of encouraging research on problems that "lie between, or are germane to, both the biological and social sciences."
In 1972 the Association changed its name to the Foundation for Child Development (FCD) to reflect its role as a grant-making organization and in particular its evolved focus on child development. Included within its mission were goals of preventing child poverty and promoting the economic stability of families. The Foundation developed several new program areas; appointed Staff Scientists, enabling specialists in child development to pursue research while simultaneously contributing to the Foundation's mission; and, most particularly, awarded grants in areas that linked research to policy, program, and leadership development. During the mid-1970s grants focused upon methods that would transfer knowledge from scholarly endeavor to government policy-makers. The George Washington University, Vanderbilt University, and the University of California at Los Angeles benefited from this support. In 1976 the Foundation published the pioneering report on The State of the Child: New York City, by Trude Lash and Heidi Sigal. Revised regularly, the report examined the indicators that reveal changes in the conditions of children's lives. In 1977, the Foundation released the preliminary findings of the National Survey of Children, directed by Nicholas Zill. This report compiled nationwide findings of interview responses from more than 2,200 pre-teens, from the ages of 7-11, and more than 1,700 of their parents’ responses. These ground-breaking survey results spoke of the attitudes, fears, and social temper of a generation.
In early 1972, Dr. Mary Jo Kline from the Columbia University Oral History Research Office conducted oral history interviews with eleven council members about the Foundation’s development after World War II. The original intent was to undertake a complete history of the organization by combining portions of the interviews with information from the Foundation's archives, but this project was never completed.
By 1980, the Foundation’s annual assets were approximately $30 million; annual grant expenditures were in the vicinity of $2 million. Around this time, the Foundation shifted focus to include examination of the causes of debilitating physical conditions and funded projects focused upon research, demonstration, and education. The formation in 1979 of Child Trends, Inc., which aimed "to improve the quality, scope and use of statistical information concerning children," reflected the FCD’s expanded goals.
The Foundation for Child Development is a national private philanthropy dedicated to the principle that all families should have the social and material resources to raise their children to be healthy, educated, and productive members of their communities. The Foundation seeks to understand children, particularly the disadvantaged, and to promote their well-being. They believe that families, schools, nonprofit organizations, businesses, and government at all levels share complementary responsibilities in the critical task of raising new generations.
The Foundation sponsors basic and policy-relevant research about the factors that promote the optimal development of children and adolescents; policy analysis, advocacy, services, and public education to enhance the discussion and adoption of social policies that support families in their important child-raising responsibilities; and leadership development activities linked to the programmatic focus of the Foundation. The Foundation believes that by integrating these approaches, it will strengthen its effectiveness in achieving its mission.
This broad statement further demonstrates the Foundation’s special interest in accommodating working families with children, who are struggling to meet their basic needs. Three themes mark Foundation support in the late twentieth century: linking research on children and families to form relevant programs and activities; isolating new approaches to devising social strategies for children and families; and increasing availability and access to early education programs and health care for children.
The Foundation hoped to compensate for the reduction in government-supported programs for children at risk by focusing more closely upon programs which would have a direct impact upon both children and families, with its research and action in this direction geared toward influencing public policy.
Scope and Contents note
Correspondents include Barbara Blum; Herbert G. Birch; Orville G. Brim, Jr.; Urie Bronfenbrenner; Hilary Rodham Clinton; Lewis B. Cuyler; Charles Dollard; Jessie Emmet; Nevil Ford; Alice FitzGerald; Charlayne Hunter Gault; George J. Hecht; Mavis Hetherington; Jerome Kagan; Sheila Kamerman; Trude Lash; Emily McFarland; Leonard Mayo; Evelyn Moore; Kathleen Mortimer; Emil Pattberg; Stephen A. Richardson; Mary French Rockefeller; Milton J. E. Senn; Heidi Sigal; Chester Swinyard; Ruby Takanishi; Ray Valdivieso; George Wheatley; and Nicholas Zill.
Conditions Governing Access
Records are open for scholarly research without restriction.
Audio cassette tapes of oral history interviews are closed to scholarly research. Conditions of access and duplication of oral history interviews are managed through Columbia University's Oral History Research Office.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
The records of the Foundation for Child Development were transferred to the Rockefeller Archive Center in 1998, 1999, and 2004.
Related Archival Materials note
Related materials may be found in:
The Foundation for Child Development (Guild for Crippled Children of the Poor of New York City) records (RAC); The Leonard Mayo papers, at the University of Minnesota, Twin Cities; the New York City Board of Education records, at Teachers College, Columbia University; the Russell Sage Foundation records (RAC); the Social Science Research Council records (RAC); and the William T. Grant Foundation records (RAC).
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be closed to research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment
Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be closed to researchers at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/Head of Reference.
Other Finding Aids
FA405 Foundation for Child Development (Guild for Crippled Children of the Poor of New York City) records
Philanthropy; Public policy; Medical care; Public health; Charities; Philanthropy -- United States; Charitable uses, trusts, and foundations; New York (N.Y.); Social service; Child development; Takanishi, Ruby; Zill, Nicholas; Wheatley, George M.; Cuyler, Lewis Baker; Clinton, Hillary Rodham; Emmet, Jessie K.; Dollard, Charles, 1907-1977; Birch, Herbert George, 1918-1973; Association for the Aid of Crippled Children; Foundation for Child Development; Blum, Barbara B.; Valdivieso, Rafael (Ray); Swinyard, Chester A.; Senn, Milton J. E.; Sigal, Heidi; Moore, Evelyn; Richardson, Stephen A.; Lash, Trude W.; Kamerman, Sheila B.; Kagan, Jerome; Rockefeller, Mary French; Hetherington, E. Mavis (Eileen Mavis), 1926-; Hunter-Gault, Charlayne; Hecht, George J.; Brim, Orville Gilbert, 1883-1987; Bronfenbrenner, Urie, 1917-2005
- Administration, 1950-1996; bulk; 1
  Arrangement note
  This series is arranged in 4 subseries:
  Subseries 1 - Board of Directors Meetings
  Subseries 2 - Committees
  Subseries 3 - Council
  Subseries 4 - President's Files, Barbara Blum
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  The archival material has been reformatted and the original records are no longer available. User copies of the microfilm are available for scholarly access.
  - Administration - Board of Directors Meetings, 1951-1996; bulk; 1
    Related Materials
    For records documenting the early administrative history of the Foundation for Child Development including its origins as the Guild for Crippled Children of the Poor of New York City and its later incarnation as the Association for the Aid of Crippled Children 1904-1914, 1919-1920, 1931-1933 please refer to the RAC copy of the Foundation for Child Development (Guild for Crippled Children of the Poor of New York City) records (FA405).
    - May 16, 1951 (Reel 2, Frame 1)
    - November 9, 1951 (Reel 2, Frame 3)
    - January 21, 1953 (Reel 2, Frame 12)
    - January 20, 1954 (Reel 2, Frame 21)
    - October 20, 1954 (Reel 2, Frame 57)
    - December 15, 1954 (Reel 2, Frame 87)
    - January 16, 1957 (Reel 2, Frame 99)
    - February 20, 1957 (Reel 2, Frame 110)
    - March 20, 1957 (Reel 2, Frame 118)
    - April 17, 1957 (Reel 2, Frame 127)
    - May 15, 1957 (Reel 2, Frame 153)
    - October 16, 1957 (Reel 2, Frame 170)
    - February 19, 1958 (Reel 2, Frame 184)
    - April 13, 1960 (Reel 2, Frame 199)
    - May 18, 1960 (Reel 2, Frame 215)
    - December 14, 1960 (Reel 2, Frame 298)
    - February 15, 1961 (Reel 2, Frame 372)
    - October 19, 1960 (Reel 2, Frame 409)
    - April 26, 1961 (Reel 2, Frame 501)
    - May 24, 1961 (Reel 2, Frame 553)
    - October 18, 1961 (Reel 2, Frame 620)
    - January 17, 1962 (Reel 2, Frame 689)
    - March 21, 1962 (Reel 2, Frame 730)
    - April 18, 1962 (Reel 2, Frame 767)
    - May 16, 1962 (Reel 2, Frame 826)
    - October 15, 1962 (Reel 2, Frame 893)
    - January 9, 1963 (Reel 2, Frame 957)
    - February 18, 1963 (Reel 2, Frame 1001)
    - March 26, 1963 (Reel 2, Frame 1045)
    - Annual Meeting, April 23, 1963 (Reel 3, Frame 4)
    - May 28, 1963 (Reel 3, Frame 48)
    - October 22, 1963 (Reel 3, Frame 112)
    - March 16, 1964 (Reel 3, Frame 201)
    - Annual Meeting, April 20, 1964 (Reel 3, Frame 263)
    - May 18, 1964 (Reel 3, Frame 317)
    - October 19, 1964 (Reel 3, Frame 362)
    - January 18, 1965 (Reel 3, Frame 454)
    - March 15, 1965 (Reel 3, Frame 532)
    - Annual Meeting, April 19, 1965 (Reel 3, Frame 599)
    - May 17, 1965 (Reel 3, Frame 628)
    - October 18, 1965 (Reel 3, Frame 695)
    - January 17, 1966 (Reel 3, Frame 721)
    - March 21, 1966 (Reel 3, Frame 754)
    - Annual Meeting, April 18, 1966 (Reel 3, Frame 789)
    - May 16, 1966 (Reel 3, Frame 793)
    - June 20, 1966 (Reel 3, Frame 864)
    - October 17, 1966 (Reel 3, Frame 909)
    - November 21, 1966 (Reel 3, Frame 917)
    - January 16, 1967 (Reel 3, Frame 972)
    - March 20, 1967 (Reel 3, Frame 1016)
    - April 17, 1967 (Reel 3, Frame 1074)
    - May 15, 1967 (Reel 3, Frame 1088)
    - September 6, 1967 (Reel 4, Frame 4)
      Scope and Contents note
      Grants 385-392
    - October 17, 1967 (Reel 4, Frame 77)
    - November 21, 1967 (Reel 4, Frame 138)
    - January 16, 1968 (Reel 4, Frame 149)
    - March 19, 1968 (Reel 4, Frame 175)
    - April 16, 1968 (Reel 4, Frame 238)
    - May 21, 1968 (Reel 4, Frame 245)
      Grants 398-402
    - October 21, 1968 (Reel 4, Frame 325)
    - January 20, 1969 (Reel 4, Frame 348)
    - March 17, 1969 (Reel 4, Frame 388)
      Grant 425
    - April 21, 1969 (Reel 4, Frame 441)
    - May 19, 1969 (Reel 4, Frame 452)
      Grants 428-433, 438
    - June 16, 1969 (Reel 4, Frame 529)
      Grants 440-443
    - October 13, 1969 (Reel 4, Frame 578)
      Grants 445-447
    - November 10, 1969 (Reel 4, Frame 641)
    - January 12, 1970 (Reel 4, Frame 644)
    - March 9, 1970 (Reel 4, Frame 687)
      Grants 459-464
    - April 13, 1970 (Reel 4, Frame 792)
      Grant 466
    - May 11, 1970 (Reel 4, Frame 811)
      Grant 448, 465, 467
    - September 24, 1970 (Reel 4, Frame 855)
      Grants 468, 472-478
    - September 24, 1970 (Reel 4, Frame 973)
      Grants 480, 481
    - January 28, 1971 (Reel 4, Frame 1025)
      Grants 484-496
    - March 25, 1971 (Reel 5, Frame 4)
    - April 22, 1971 (Reel 5, Frame 101)
    - May 27, 1971 (Reel 5, Frame 120)
    - September 23, 1971 (Reel 5, Frame 231)
    - December 2, 1971 (Reel 5, Frame 342)
    - January 27, 1972 (Reel 5, Frame 460)
    - March 23, 1972 (Reel 5, Frame 535)
    - May 25, 1972 (Reel 5, Frame 673)
    - September 28, 1972 (Reel 5, Frame 768)
    - November 30, 1972 (Reel 5, Frame 924)
    - January 25, 1973 (Reel 6, Frame 4)
    - March 23, 1973 (Reel 6, Frame 38)
    - May 15, 1973 (Reel 6, Frame 112)
    - June 26, 1973 (Reel 6, Frame 205)
    - July 5, 1973 (Reel 6, Frame 221)
    - July 11, 1973 (Reel 6, Frame 244)
    - July 18, 1973 (Reel 6, Frame 248)
    - July 26, 1973 (Reel 6, Frame 254)
    - Annual Meeting, September 25, 1973 (Reel 6, Frame 259)
      Grants 533-536
    - November 29, 1973 (Reel 6, Frame 348)
      Grants 537-540
    - January 24, 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 447)
    - February 20, 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 480)
    - March 28, 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 493)
    - May 14, 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 534)
    - Annual Meeting, September 18, 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 628)
    - December 5, 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 695)
    - February 27, 1975 (Reel 6, Frame 843)
    - May 22, 1975 (Reel 6, Frame 965)
    - Annual Meeting, September 17, 1975 (Reel 7, Frame 4)
    - December 4, 1975 (Reel 7, Frame 164)
    - March 4, 1976 (Reel 7, Frame 291)
    - June 3, 1976 (Reel 7, Frame 467)
    - September 15, 1976 (Reel 7, Frame 598)
    - December 2, 1976 (Reel 7, Frame 741)
    - March 3, 1977 (Reel 7, Frame 836)
    - June 2, 1977 (Reel 7, Frame 965)
    - Annual Meeting, September 14, 1977 (Reel 8, Frame 4)
    - December 8, 1977 (Reel 8, Frame 342)
    - March 2, 1978 (Reel 8, Frame 456)
    - June 1, 1978 (Reel 8, Frame 656)
    - Annual Meeting, September 20, 1978 (Reel 8, Frame 961)
    - December 7, 1978 (Reel 9, Frame 4)
    - March 1, 1979 (Reel 9, Frame 120)
    - June 7, 1979 (Reel 9, Frame 275)
    - Annual Meeting, September 19, 1979 (Reel 9, Frame 458)
    - June 7, 1979 (Reel 9, Frame 639)
    - March 6, 1980 (Reel 9, Frame 844)
    - June 11, 1980 (Reel 10, Frame 4)
    - Annual Meeting, September 25, 1980 (Reel 10, Frame 197)
    - December 4, 1980 (Reel 10, Frame 368)
    - March 5, 1981 (Reel 10, Frame 560)
    - June 4, 1981 (Reel 11, Frame 4)
    - Annual Meeting, September 24, 1981 (Reel 11, Frame 293)
    - December 3, 1981 (Reel 11, Frame 401)
    - March 4, 1982 (Reel 11, Frame 627)
    - June 3, 1982 (Reel 11, Frame 925)
    - Annual Meeting, September 23, 1982 (Reel 12, Frame 4)
    - December 2, 1982 (Reel 12, Frame 352)
    - March 3, 1983 (Reel 12, Frame 718)
    - June 2, 1983 (Reel 12, Frame 939)
    - Annual Meeting, September 22, 1983 (Reel 13, Frame 4)
    - December 8, 1983 (Reel 13, Frame 157)
    - March 1, 1984 (Reel 13, Frame 337)
    - June 7, 1984 (Reel 13, Frame 513)
    - Annual Meeting, September 20, 1984 (Reel 13, Frame 623)
    - December 6, 1984 (Reel 13, Frame 772)
    - March 7, 1985 (Reel 13, Frame 860)
    - June 6, 1985 (Reel 14, Frame 4)
    - Annual Meeting, September 26, 1985 (Reel 14, Frame 170)
    - December 5, 1985 (Reel 14, Frame 286)
    - March 6, 1986 (Reel 14, Frame 603)
    - June 5, 1986 (Reel 14, Frame 821)
    - Annual Meeting, September 25, 1986 (Reel 14, Frame 946)
    - December 4, 1986 (Reel 15, Frame 4)
    - March 5, 1987 (Reel 15, Frame 257)
    - June 11, 1987 (Reel 15, Frame 676)
    - Annual Meeting, September 17, 1987 (Reel 16, Frame 4)
    - December 3, 1987 (Reel 16, Frame 198)
    - March 3, 1987 (Reel 16, Frame 344)
    - June 9, 1988 (Reel 16, Frame 523)
    - Annual Meeting, September 15, 1988 (Reel 16, Frame 739)
    - December 1, 1988 (Reel 17, Frame 4)
    - March 2, 1989 (Reel 17, Frame 311)
    - June 8, 1989 (Reel 17, Frame 556)
    - September 21, 1989 (Reel 17, Frame 768)
    - December 7, 1989 (Reel 18, Frame 4)
    - March 1, 1990 (Reel 18, Frame 182)
    - June 14, 1990 (Reel 18, Frame 329)
    - Annual Meeting, September 27, 1990 (Reel 18, Frame 603)
    - December 6, 1990 (Reel 18, Frame 727)
    - March 7, 1991 (Reel 18, Frame 845)
    - March 5, 1992 (Reel 18, Frame 849)
    - June 11, 1992 (Reel 18, Frame 873)
    - September 24, 1992 (Reel 18, Frame 916)
    - June 10, 1993 (Reel 18, Frame 928)
    - June 9, 1994 (Reel 18, Frame 960)
    - December 7, 1995 (Reel 18, Frame 1026)
    - March 7, 1996 (Reel 18, Frame 1044)
    - June 6, 1996 (Reel 18, Frame 1062)
    - Mailing Lists, 1968-1972 (Reel 18, Frame 1083)
  - Administration - Committees, 1950-1992, 1996; bulk; 2
    This subseries contains the notes and minutes of the Executive, Nominating, Personnel, Financial, and several ad hoc committees.
    - Ad-Hoc Committee on the Administrative Costs of Grants, 1980-1982 (Reel 19, Frame 4)
    - Ad-Hoc Committee on Investment Policy, 1971 (Reel 19, Frame 250)
    - Ad-Hoc Committee - Resolution, Robert J. Slater, 1965-1968 (Reel 19, Frame 276)
    - Audit Committee, 1965-1978, 1990-1992 (Reel 19, Frame 286)
    - Executive Committee, June 15, 1950 (Reel 19, Frame 334)
    - Executive Committee, October 11, 1950 (Reel 19, Frame 347)
    - Pension and Executive Committee, June 20, 1951 (Reel 19, Frame 384)
    - Executive Committee, March 14, 1952 (Reel 19, Frame 387)
    - Executive Committee, October 8, 1952 (Reel 19, Frame 393)
    - Executive Committee, February 5, 1953 (Reel 19, Frame 395)
    - Executive Committee, March 18, 1953 (Reel 19, Frame 402)
    - Executive Committee, February 17, 1954 (Reel 19, Frame 409)
    - Executive Committee, January 16, 1955 (Reel 19, Frame 413)
    - Executive Committee, February 15, 1955 (Reel 19, Frame 419)
    - Executive Committee, June 15, 1955 (Reel 19, Frame 426)
    - Executive Committee, December 14, 1955 (Reel 19, Frame 438)
    - Executive Committee, February 3, 1956 (Reel 19, Frame 460)
    - Executive Committee, December 6, 1956 (Reel 19, Frame 474)
    - Executive Committee, February 13, 1957 (Reel 19, Frame 503)
    - Executive Committee, June 3, 1957 (Reel 19, Frame 510)
    - Executive Committee, May 2, 1958 (Reel 19, Frame 516)
    - Executive Committee, August 28, 1958 (Reel 19, Frame 528)
    - Executive Committee, September 30, 1959 (Reel 19, Frame 545)
    - Executive Committee, April 20, 1960 (Reel 19, Frame 571)
    - Executive Committee, June 21, 1960 (Reel 19, Frame 612)
    - Executive Committee, November 16, 1960 (Reel 19, Frame 629)
    - Executive Committee, January 18, 1961 (Reel 19, Frame 648)
    - Executive Committee, March 15, 1961 (Reel 19, Frame 689)
    - Executive Committee, July 19, 1961 (Reel 19, Frame 773)
    - Executive Committee, November 15, 1961 (Reel 19, Frame 815)
    - Executive Committee, December 13, 1961 (Reel 19, Frame 849)
    - Executive Committee, February 21, 1962 (Reel 19, Frame 868)
    - Executive Committee, June 18, 1962 (Reel 19, Frame 905)
    - Executive Committee, December 10, 1962 (Reel 19, Frame 942)
    - Executive Committee, June 20, 1963 (Reel 19, Frame 1049)
    - Executive Committee, November 25, 1963 (Reel 19, Frame 1087)
    - Executive Committee, January 28, 1964 (Reel 20, Frame 4)
    - Executive Committee, February 26, 1964 (Reel 20, Frame 57)
    - Executive Committee, April 20, 1964 (Reel 20, Frame 137)
    - Executive Committee, May 18, 1964 (Reel 20, Frame 151)
    - Executive Committee, June 15, 1964 (Reel 20, Frame 153)
    - Executive Committee, August 31, 1964 (Reel 20, Frame 210)
    - Executive Committee, November 16, 1964 (Reel 20, Frame 230)
    - Executive Committee, December 14, 1964 (Reel 20, Frame 268)